他们的表演 是大多数常人从未见过的
It is a spectacle unlike most have ever witnessed.
有来自非洲深处 文明人不曾见过的生物
Creatures from the darkest Africa as yet unseen by civilized man.
来自东方的杂耍人
Acrobats from the Orient
能将自己扭曲成各种形状
who contort themselves in the most confounding manners.
而我则是布朗先生的副手
And I myself in aide of Mr. Brown,
他是享誉国际的
an internationally renowned practitioner
一名魔术师
in the art of prestidigitation.
我们现在正要回公司去
We are on our way thither to rejoin the company,
我们短时间离开
having left for a short time
是希望从自己的演出中获取薄利
to make a small profit from our own exhibitions.
我们向穆恩先生打听是因为…
The reason for our inquiry with Mr. Moon...
是的 我们苦于找不到
Yes. We had just a devil of a time
适合我们演出的音乐
in procuring music for our entertainments.
似乎真正有才能的人少之又少
Men of true talents are seemingly in short supply.
多谢称赞 先生
Thank you, sir.